emagister.in 2012-10-16

# Emagister

This privacy policy governs the use of the Website www.emagister.in (the "Website").

As set out in the organic law 15/1999, dated 13th December, for Personal Data Protection (LOPD), we inform our Users of the existence of an automated database used to store personal information, created by and sole responsibility of EMAGISTER. 

**2\. Our use of your personal information**

Information on registered users collected from the registration forms on the website are obtained by EMAGISTER for the sole purpose of devlivering the services offered via the Website: that is, to act as a link between course providers and users, provide information on courses, publications and other relevant services that may be of interest to the User. 

**3\. Optional and compulsory information**

Fields marked with an asterisk (*) on the user registration form must be completed in order for requests to be processed. The other fields are optional. 

The user guarantees that the information provided is truthful and is responsible for informing us of any changes and keeping it up-to-date. 

**4\. User consent**

The submission of personal information via EMAGISTERs electronic forms, or where appropriate, via e-mail, implies the express consent of the sender for the information included to undergo automated processes and to receive e-mails with information related to the EMAGISTER and the services and products it offers.

The User also gives consent to EMAGISTER to send information to third parties in order for the service requested to be carried out. In this respect, a Third Party refers to "entities that use EMAGISTER to find users interested in courses ". 

**5\. Newsletter and Electronic communication**

EMAGISTER sends users who have given their prior consent on the registration form a newsletter which includes the most relevant information and news on the Website. The user can also edit their information or unsubscribe from the newsletter through an interactive file on the Website.

EMAGISTER will send electronic commercial communications with information on other products, services and events that may be of interest to the User, when expressly requested. Consent to receiving these communications can be cancelled at any time.

EMAGISTER offers two simple and free ways in which to unsubscribe from this service. The User should login to their menu, untick the send option in the e-mail communications field. Likewise, you can also unsubscribe by following the instructions at the bottom of each communication received. 

**6\. Emagister International**

The User also gives express consent for the information submitted to be shared with firms within the Group of companies that Emagister forms a part of, either national or international (Grupo Emagister Internacional).

In this regard, EMAGISTER and Grupo Emagister Internacional are committed to making responsible and confidential use of the information provided by Users, ensuring it is used within the relevant legal framework and only in the context of Emagister with the aims indicated. 

**7\. Security**

EMAGISTER maintains the personal data protection security levels established by Royal Decree 994/1999, 11th June, in reference to the security measures required for automated files with content of a personal nature, and has put all the necessary technical measures in place in order to avoid the loss, misuse, altering, unauthorised access or theft of information provided by Users via the Website, whilst informing that Internet security measures are not impregnable.

EMAGISTER is committed to maintaining confidentiality with regard to the personal information included in the automated file, in compliance with the relevant legislation, and to providing secure treatment in any international data transfer procedures that may arise. 

**8\. Cookies and IPs**

The User accepts the use of cookies and IP monitoring. Our traffic analyst uses cookies and IP monitoring to gather statistical data such as: date of first visit, number of visits, date of last visit, source URL and domain, explorer used and screen resolution. However, if desired, the User can de-activate and/ or delete these cookies by following the instructions on their Internet navigator.

Emagister is subscribed to "Google AdSense", an advertising system which uses cookies to display publicity related to site visitor browsing habits. When a visitor enters a site subscribed to "Google AdSense", a cookie is added to their browser from which Google gathers information in order to publish relevant ads that may be of interest. Site visitors can disable the use of cookies by Google at any time using the cookies option in their browser. 

EMAGISTER does not use spamming techniques and will only deal with information that the User provides through the electronic forms on the Website or by e-mail.

The use of information of a personal nature and the sending of electronic commercial communications comply with the organic law for Personal Data Protection 15/1999, dated 13th December (B.O.E. 14th December 1999) and Regulation 34/2002 of the Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce Regulations, dated 11th July (B.O.E. 12th July 2002). 

**9\. Right of Access, Opposition, Cancellation and Rectification**

The user has the right to access and modify this information or unsubscribe from EMAGISTERs services.

These rights can be exercised through the configuration of the webpage itself. In case of problems exercising these rights online, or of any other type of doubt or query regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at the following address:

Communications Department  
infoemagister.in  
EMAGISTER  
Edificio Testa, Avenida Alcalde Barnils 64- 68, D, 4a planta,  
08174 - Sant Cugat del Valles  
Barcelona

All treatment of personal information and communications made by electronic means meets the legal requirements established in the organic law 15/1999, dated 13th December, for Personal Data Protection (B.O.E 14/12/1999) and in regulation 34/2002, dated 11th July, of the Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce Regulations (B.O.E. 12/07/2002). 

**10\. Amendment of the Privacy Policy**

EMAGISTER reserves the right to modify this policy, adapt it to future legislative regulations or jurisprudence and to industry practices.
